Where am I?
Well!
Hello everyone!
I'm here at Noevir Stadium
Today, we are going to have a kick-in ceremony.
I'm going to hold a kick-in ceremony
I'll be doing the kick-in ceremony.
I'm very nervous, but
but I'm going to give it my all.
I'm going to give it my all.
Please take a look at the other side of my nerves.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for watching!
My name is Yukimao, from Osaka 46. I was born and raised in Kobe, and I love this city full of nature and exotic atmosphere.
The pace is too standard.
It makes me nervous.
It's something more than a live concert venue.
I could see everything up there.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thanks for your hard work.
Thank you very much
Big whistles!
You did great!
Are you okay?
You did good.
It's a nice course.
Yeah, I had it done, but...
What?
Huh.huh?
I'm scared.
What do you remember?
What do you remember? But...
I remember seeing it from a very high seat.
It's so far away.
That's great.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for waiting.
That's great.
That's amazing.
I'm so happy.
Someone else is wearing the same uniform.
Let's blend in a little bit.
The manager...
He just bumped into me.
He's asking for you.
I need to see him.
What's this?
It's a collaboration with Familia.
I'd like to buy some of these. They asked for them.
I miss Familia.
This looks like fun. I'll give it a try.
Can I open it?
Open it later.
I'd like to play with it later.I'd like to mess this up a little later.
So this is how it's going to be.
It's nice... before the game.
Did you come here when you were a kid?
I came here when I was a kid.
This... this reminds me so much of this feeling.
I remember.
I don't remember what I ate.
Next time
I don't really remember eating this menu.
I'm so happy!
Bon appétit!
It's so good!
So much oil on it!
What's this?
Chicken!
That's the best chicken I've ever had!
I love this kind of scenery so much.
But it feels like it's been a long time since I've had it.
I'm going to have to go back to the tea bowl.
I'm going to be a goddess of victory!
I'm so happy.
That's amazing.
It's so similar. It's so good!
I don't know what this taremint thing is, but that's what this taremint thing said.
I don't know, I think it worked out great for me.
Wait a minute.
Last but not least, the players of the press ring walk!Finally, to all the players in the Presling Walk
I support J1 League and Free Myself Kili as much as I can!
Good luck!
That's all for now, this is Mao Yuki.
Thank you very much.
Not too much.
There is too much power.
Too much power.
Oh, my God.
I'm really surprised at how much you play with it.
It's okay.
Well, today we have a special guest, a member of Nogizaka Home Exinx from Kobe City.
Maho Ioki, who is from Kobe City, is here at Koemura Stadium Kobe.
Please give a big round of applause!
Nogizaka Home Exinx member from Kobe City
Home Exinx member from Kobe City
Hello everyone.
I am Mamo Iosaka from Toyonaka 46.
I'm Mamo Ioaki, a member of Toyonaka 46.
I was born and raised in Kobe City.
I grew up in Kobe City.
full of nature and
I love this city
I love this city.
I love this cityIn such a city
There is a soccer team
Vissel Cocoa's game.
I am very happy to be back here
I am very happy to be back here.
And to Yokohama
in a car for an emergency stop as well.
I will play against them.
I did my best.
I did my best, I did my best.
It's really off.
I was chewing.
But you got what I wanted to say, so it's okay.
I got through.
One stop.
If it's a reward, it's enough to get in.
Entelemony.
Are you okay?
Les Bangs.
I think he made it.
This one.
This one was actually made for me.
No. 96, the Lyoki Mao uniform.
Cute.
So cute!
I'm so happy.
Well then, I look forward to working with you, Mr. Rio Kumao.
I'll make love to you, fill-in-fill-in
you were amazingly good.
I'm a lot more nervous than I was when I ate it earlier.I'm a lot more nervous than I was earlier when I was eating.
Here's Taichu watching you now.
Bon appétit!
Kirby.
Later.
We're going to play PK together.
Next, I'd like to open
I'd like to open a random race.
This is a coving pudding sticker!
Yes!
First,
Stick out the sticker until you win.
I wish you all the best.
Next time we accept, we'll stick out until we win.
And this time, it's our very own Moby who's going to take out the keeper.
Yes, Moby.
How confident are you, by the way?
I'm not very confident.
But I've just learned from a player.
I'm going to do my best with that advice in mind.
I understand. Please do your best.
Yes, I will.
But Moby hates to lose.
This is a match that's up for grabs, so please do your best.
Now, before the penalty shootout, please shake hands and pledge your swords to each other.
Yes, sir.
And now, it's time for the penalty shootout.
On my cue, let's begin.
We now go to the penalty kick challenge by Mao Ioki, a member of Nogizaka46 from Kobe City.Here we go, a PK challenge by Mao Ioki, a member of Nogizaka46 from Kobe City!
This is a PK challenge by Mao Ioki, a member of Nogizaka46 from Kobe!
Yamato Shogun
Legendary Object
Break
Michon Commit
Hitlow Shopping
Amazing!
Beautiful.
Really.
Obi-kun avoided me.
LOL.
Okay, everyone's.
LOL!
Hey, Obi-kun, he's here.
Thank you.
Obi-kun avoided me.
LOL.
I went straight and clean.
I've already made Beef nervous.
Now, I'm a pervert.
Now it's all over.
I did a lot of things, starting with the first greeting.
I was so nervous at the first greeting.
I hadn't been that nervous in a really long time.
But everyone was so warm that I was glad to have hot water.
I was also very happy to be able to use the hot water. During the kick-in ceremony, I could feel the aura and power of the players.
It was a really valuable experience for me, and I am very grateful for it.
The B-class showdown was a lot of fun!
I had such a great experience with Mr. Moby on the lawn of such a great venue.Mr. Moby and I had such an experience on the lawn of such an amazing venue.
I really enjoyed the whole day!
Thank you very much for this valuable experience!
I'm really happy that you made this for me too!
Thank you for watching to the end!
Lastly, please subscribe to our channel, click the Good button, and give us a high rating!
See you again!
Ending